

Taipei City, Taiwan

Profile .

Hi, I am KuanYen Huang, a game developer from Taiwan who wants to bring the best game experience to all players. I have years of experience developing game projects mostly using C# & Unity. In the various game projects I've worked on, I've not only worked as a game programmer but also taken on roles such as game designer and project manager. Along with these experiences, I've developed strong collaboration skills and independence as a developer.

Education _

National Tsing Hua University

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

• Overall GPA: 3.72 / 4.3

Hsinchu, Taiwan Sep 2020 - Jun 2024

Experience _

CreSpirit

Hsinchu, Taiwan

Game Programmer and Designer Intern
Feb 2024 – Jun 2024

- Working on a prototype of an ongoing project's mini-game.
- Supporting several design tasks including multi-language data and mini-game design.

VL Lab - National Tsing Hua University

Hsinchu, Taiwan

INDEPENDENT STUDY: Development of Unique Turn Base Combat Game "Project Fusion"

Feb 2023 - Jan2024

- Developed a prototype of "Project Fusion".
- Construct a skill part-based system, can create and modify skill's attributes and effects only using texts via Google spreadsheet.

Projects _

Project Fusion

Leader, Programmer, Designer

Apr 2023 - Present

- Current ongoing project began from independent study, an auto battler game featuring a unique fusing artifact mechanic.
- Recreat gameplay ability system from Unreal Engine to Unity and modified it to fit the game more.

Duplicate Solution Unacceptable (GMTK Jam 2024)

SOLO DEVELOPMENT Aug 2024

• First time using Godot to create an easy puzzle during GMTK Jam 2024, with the theme of "Build to Scale".

Deal Da Time (GMTK Jam 2023)

LEADER, PROGRAMMER, DESIGNER

Jul 2023

• A mini puzzle game that was created during GMTK Jam 2023, with the theme of "Role Reversed".

You Ken-Do It

LEADER, PROGRAMMER, DESIGNER

Mar 2023 - Jun 2023

- A VR kendo game made by Unity focused on Block & Counter mechanic with slashing system from Metal Gear Rising: Revengeance.
- Program and design the user interface and experience in VR.
- Awarded in the competition of VR project among three Taiwan universities.

OCTOBER 9, 2024 KUANYEN HUANG · RESUME 1

Survivor For the Feast

LEADER, PROGRAMMER, DESIGNER, ART

Sep 2022 - Jan 2023

- A survivor game made by Unity in which you need to collect ingredients to make dishes.
- Working as the leader and applying agile methodology to manage project.
- Winning Best Game Design in Taiwan Student Innovation Game Design Competition 2023 and Best Game in the course presentation.

An Extra Ordinary YouTube Video

LEADER, PROGRAMMER, DESIGNER

Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

- A bullet hell action game made by Cocos with a unique mechanic that you can rewind the boss fight via video progress bar.
- Using the instruction-based Boss script and object pooling bullet to implement level editor, making the whole level rewindable.

Lost in Dungeon (Global Game Jam 2021)

PROGRAMMER, DESIGNER

Jan 2021

- A dungeon crawling action game made by Unity created during Global Game Jam 2021, with the theme of "Lost and Found".
- Programming the map generator and designing several design tasks.

duRNGeon

SOLO DEVELOPMENT

Mar 2019 - Apr 2019

• A dungeon crawler rogue-like game made by Unity which player could control RNG.

Guillemets

SOLO DEVELOPMENT

Apr 2018 - May 2018

• A horror visual novel on mobile made by Unity with puzzles involving multi-ending.

Honor & Awards

Jun 2023, **Awarded** in the competition of VR project among three Taiwan universities Jan 2023, **Best Game Design** in Taiwan Student Innovation Game Design Competition

Jan 2023, **Best Game** in Game Development Course at National Tsing Hua University

Skills

Languages: C#, Unity, Cocos, Python, C, C++, Godot, HTML **English:** TOEFL — 106/120 (*R*:30/30, *L*:29/30, *S*:23/30, *W*:24/30)